Guide to the National Lesbian and Gay Health Association records, 1978-1992.
National Lesbian and Gay Health Association records,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
National Lesbian and Gay Health Association records, 1978-1992
7613
National Lesbian and Gay Health Association
16.1 cubic ft.
Correspondence, subject files, records, publications, audiotapes, videotapes.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, subject files, minutes, financial records, conference planning files, publications, proposals, audio recordings, and videocassettes of the National Lesbian and Gay Health Foundation and the Federation of AIDS Related Organizations (FARO).
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The National Lesbian and Gay Health Foundation (founded 1977) and the Alliance of Lesbian and Gay Health Clinics (founded 1992) merged in June of 1994 to form the National Lesbian and Gay Health Association. It was a part of the Federation of AIDS Related Organizations (FARO) and sponsored annual conferences for lesbian, bisexual, and gay health workers. The Lesbian and Gay Health Conference and AIDS/HIV Forum provided opportunities to share research data and program expertise. NLGHA created a National Research Institute for Lesbian and Gay Health to assist health professionals in designing research, identifying funding opportunities, and communicating research findings. Located in Washington, NLGHA also advocated at the federal level on health issues facing the lesbian, bisexual, and gay community: breast and cervical cancer; STDs; hepatitis; substance abuse; mental health; lbg-related violence; suicide; and HIV/AIDS. A scholarship in honor of Paul Paroski Jr. was created and began to be offered to support lesbian and gay medical students in 1991. In 1997, NLGHA published The Gay Men's Wellness Guide: The National Lesbian and Gay Health Association's Complete Book of Physical, Emotional and Mental Health and Well-Being for Every Gay Male. The organization had financial and administrative difficulties and closed sometime between 1997 and 2002.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, subject files, minutes, financial records, conference planning files, publications, proposals, audio recordings, and videocassettes of the National Lesbian and Gay Health Foundation and the Federation of AIDS Related Organizations (FARO).
SUBJECTS
Names:
National Lesbian and Gay Health Association; AIDS/HIV Forum.; Alliance of Lesbian and Gay Health Association (U.S.); National Lesbian and Gay Health Foundation
Subjects:
Health promotion--Gays; Health promotion--Lesbians.; Health--Education; AIDS (Disease)--Study and teaching.; AIDS (Disease)--Education
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Box 1 is RESTRICTED until 2056.
Box 1, Folder 12 may be viewed if the researcher signs a release form agreeing not to reveal the names of donators to the Paroski Scholarship fund.
RELATED MATERIALS
Collecting Program: Human Sexuality Collection
SERIES LIST
Series I. NLGHF Administrative Files
Boxes 1-3,13-14
Introductory Material
Board Materials
Staff Files
Correspondence
Financial Files
Miscellaneous
Series II. International Lesbian & Gay Health Conference & AIDS Forum Files
Boxes 1,3-10,13-14
Conference Session Cassette Recordings
Series III. Federation of AIDS Related Organizations (FARO)
Box 10
Series IV. NLGHF Publicity/Publications
Boxes 10-11,14
Series V. NLGHF Subject Files
Boxes 11-13
Topical
Organizations
Series VI. Miscellany
Box 13
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Administrative Files
  - Introductory Material
    - "How the Filing System Works", n.d. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - File inventory, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Articles of Incorporation, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - First meeting materials, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - NGHEF proposal agreement, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - By-laws, 1983? (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - NGHEF organizational development, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - By-laws, reports, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - By-laws, 1985? (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Information of NLGHF- history of the foundation, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Board Materials
    - Board materials, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Board biographies (curriculum vitae), 1983 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Board correspondence, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Board lists, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Board materials, including corespondence and board list, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Board list 1, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Board- responses to 5/84 vote, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Board- cost sharing, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Board meeting minutes, July 1985 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Board mailing list, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Reports to the board, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Board minutes, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 22-23)
    - Board meeting materials, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Board lists, general information, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Board correspondence, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Reports to the board, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Board meeting minutes, May 31, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Misc. board materials, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Board correspondence/memos, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Oversize meeting sheets- strategic planning meeting, 1989 (Mapcase-folder 1)
  - Staff Files
    - Staff: Biely, Louis, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Staff: Donnell, Cynthia, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Staff: Ladner, Shayne (change of address form), n.d. (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Staff: Roman, Bea- work and conference reports, 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Staff: Vachon, Ron, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Staff: Weeks, Michael- work and compensation issues, 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Staff: Wittlif, Marc, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Executive Director contract, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Job descriptions, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Position description form, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence
    - Sourcebook requests, budget sheets, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - General inquiries, Sourcebook and Directory requests, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: information requests, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: information requests, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Sourcebook related correspondence, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: information requests, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: information requests, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - American Public Health Association correspondence re: National Gay Health Directoy, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence, 1983-1986 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 44-45)
    - Correspondence re: office space, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Correspondnce, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Correspondence re: Upcoming board meeting, Dec. 1985 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Correspondence- letters, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Correspondence/pamphlets re: Washing Council of Agencies, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Inter-office memos, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Pharmaceutical letter, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Correspondence re: Caitlin Ryan resigantion, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Correspondence, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Correspondence, administrative, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Financial Files
    - Paroski Scholarship Fund donations, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Grants, 1976-1981 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Grants in-process, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Grant writing, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - MS grant, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - National Lesbian Health Care Survey fundraising, 1985? (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - NLGHF fundraising, 1984, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Grantmaker mailing list, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Fundraising letter, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Possible grants, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Fundraising, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - CDC grant, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - NYS 1023- exemption application, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Finances, 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - IRS 1023 Income Tax exemption application (501(c)3), 1980-1981,1990 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Financial records misc., 1980, 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - 501(c)3, 1981, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - IRS financial statements, 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Federal 990 return, 1981-1989 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Karposi, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - NGHEF Credit, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Insurance/disability (unemployment), 1983 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Payroll and taxes, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Employee disability benefits(?), 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Amalgamated Bank, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Annual report- New York State Dep't of State, 1983-1991 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Insurance- health, burglary, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Select bills due, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Creditor correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Finances, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Peter Kelly Estate, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Payment of back taxes, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - NYS Dep't of Law Annual Report, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Federal 1096 return, 1986, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Federal 1099 return, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Billing information, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Finances/taxes, 1987,1989 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - NLGHF Financial statement, Mar. 1-June 24, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Federal 941, W-3, W-2 returns, 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Virginia registration and payment, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Independent auditor's report, 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - DC application for exemption, 1988,1990 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - DC taxes- witholdings, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Paroski Benificiary notification, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Newspapers, 1982? (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Miscellaneous legal documents, 1982, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - NGHEF Liaisons, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Sample solicitation letters, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - United Way, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - NGHEF Funds, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Financial Records, 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Fundraising- direct mail appeal letter creation mock-ups, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Mailing address lists, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - National Association of People With AIDS (NAPWA) lists, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - AIDS related services list, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Communication Ads, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Communication Ad volunteers, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - NLGHF Brochure materials, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Gay Press, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Mailing lists, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Publishers, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Baltimore, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Associates forms, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Associates to process, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Awards, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Phone messages, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Zip codes count report, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Series II. Conference Files
  - Southeastern Conference for Lesbians and Gay Men registrations, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 9-10)
  - Conference 1983 registration lists, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - NGHC planning, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Conference planning materials, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Misc. conference materials, 1982-1985 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - National Lesbian and Gay Health Conference, Houston misc., June 4-6, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Audit report, Conference 1983 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - NLGHC expenditures, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - NGHEF conference 5, Denver, June 9-12, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - NLGHC Reduced Fee information, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Refunds, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Southeast Conference for Lesbians + Gay Men, correspondence with presenters, performer, and exhibitors, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Conference registration materials, Conference 1983 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - 3rd Annual AIDS Forum- Distribution of workshops, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - 1st International Lesbian/Gay Health Conference advertisement, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Advertising, Conference 1984 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Brochure, Conference 1984 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Budget, Conference 1984 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Checks returned, Conference 1984 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Communications, Conference 1984 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Display tables, Conference 1984 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Evaluations, Conference 1984 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Miscellaneous expenses, Conference 1984 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Express service, Conference 1984 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Insurance, Conference 1984 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Loan repayment, Conference 1984 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - NGHEF misc., Conference 1984 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Conference Packet, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 71-72)
  - Petty cash, Conference 1984 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Postage, Conference 1984 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Poster, Conference 1984 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Press coverage, Conference 1984 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Printing, Conference 1984 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - NGHEF Conference 6, NYC, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Registrations due, Conference 1984 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Sourcebook expenses, Conference 1984 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Staff, Conference 1984 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Supplies, Conference 1984 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Telephone, Conference 1984 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Program book/flyer mock-ups, Conference 1984 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Committee notes, Conference 1985 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - GWU correspondence, Conference 1985 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Miscellanous, Conference 1985 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Planning materials, Conference 1985 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Scientific community, Conference 1985 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - NLGHC info., 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Future conference site materials, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Alphabetical listing of presenters, Conference 1986 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Audio-visual schedule, Conference 1986 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Brochures, Conference 1986 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Conference committees, Conference 1986 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Communications: correspondence, Conference 1986 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Communications: display-space memo., Conference 1986 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Communications: form memo to/info. on presenters, Conference 1986 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Communications: grantmaker letters, Conference 1986 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Communications: GWU/CME letter of agreement, Conference 1986 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Evaluations, Conference 1986 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Exhibitors, Conference 1986 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - HTLV III testing statement, Conference 1986 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Misc. materials, Conference 1986 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Conference packet, Conference 1986 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Photographer, Conference 1986 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Postage/UPS/Federal Express, Conference 1986 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Press relations/press releases, Conference 1986 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Press list, Conference 1986 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Seventh NLGHC, Fourth National AIDS Forum program, Conference 1986 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Reciepts and reimbursement, Conference 1986 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Speakers information forms, Conference 1986 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Topical listing of presentations, Conference 1986 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Volunteers, Conference 1986 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Workshop proposals, Conference 1986 (Box 4, Folder 39-45)
  - Workshop materials, 4-5:30PM, Thursday, March 13, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Workshop materials, 10:45AM-12:15PM, Friday, March 14, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Workshop materials, 2-3:30PM, Friday, March 14, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Workshop materials, 4-5:30PM, Friday, March 14, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Workshop materials, 11:30AM-1PM, Saturday, March 15, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Workshop materials, 2-3:30PM, Saturday, March 15, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Workshop materials, 4-5:30PM, Saturday, March 15, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Program book mock-ups, photos, CAIN flyer mock-up, Conference 1986 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Addendum, Conference 1987 (Los Angeles, CA, March 26-29) (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Ads, Conference 1987 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Advertising, Conference 1987 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Award recipients letters, Conference 1987 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Banquet planning materials, Conference 1987 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Board materials, Conference 1987 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Boston Globe article, Conference 1987 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Brochure materials, Conference 1987 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Budget, Conference 1987 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Call for papers, Conference 1987 (Box 5, Folder 14-15)
  - Correspondence, Conference 1987 (Box 5, Folder 16-17)
  - Correspondence after 3/1, Conference 1987 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: Greg Thomas, Conference 1987 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence: conference director, Conference 1987 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Daily Update, Conference 1987 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Evaluations, Conference 1987 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Exhibitors, Conference 1987 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Feedback forms, Conference 1987 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Financial statements, Conference 1987 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Female health movement plenary, Conference 1987 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Housing, Conference 1987 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - John Olson, Conference 1987 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Local organizing lists, Conference 1987 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Mailings, Conference 1987 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Media, Conference 1987 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous, Conference 1987 (Box 5, Folder 32-33)
  - Organization and budgets, Conference 1987 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Originals (?), Conference 1987 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Presentation materials, Conference 1987 (Box 5, Folder 36-38)
  - Presentation proposal materials, Conference 1987 (Box 5, Folder 39-41)
  - Presentation proposal materials, Conference 1987 (Box 6, Folder 1-3)
  - Presentation (panel) materials, Conference 1987 (Box 6, Folder 4-12)
  - Press coverage, Conference 1987 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - LA press list, Conference 1987 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Press relations, Conference 1987 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - NLGHC and 5th Annual National AIDS Forum program book, Conference 1987 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Program book materials, Conference 1987 (Box 6, Folder 17-18)
  - Program book: creative development assistant, Conference 1987 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Program handbook materials, Conference 1987 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Programming- dead file, Conference 1987 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Resolutions, Conference 1987 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Resolutions approved, Conference 1987 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Scheduling of events, Conference 1987 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Scholarships, Conference 1987 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Screening committees, Conference 1987 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Sheraton Universal Hotel, Conference 1987 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Special guests, Conference 1987 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Sponsors, Conference 1987 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Tape recordings list, Conference 1987 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Travel arrangements, Conference 1987 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Program cover mock-up, Conference 1987? (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - VHS Tape: Conference closing session, Conference 1987, V-372
  - AA, NA, AlAnon, ACOA, Conference 1988 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - AAPHR, Conference 1988 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - AIDS update, Conference 1988 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Bea, Conference 1988 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Boston Nursing and Social Work fiasco: correspondence, Conference 1988 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Boston Nursing and Social Work fiasco: CEU requests, Conference 1988 (Box 7, Folder 9-12)
  - CAIN (Computerized AIDS Information Network), Conference 1988 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Call for forms, Conference 1988 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Continuing eduacation, Conference 1988 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, news reviews, Conference 1988 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Dennis McShane, Conference 1988 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Fenway Community Health Center, Conference 1988 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Forms and flyers, Conference 1988 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Fund for Human Dignity, Conference 1988 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Follow-up, Conference 1988 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Institutes, Conference 1988 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Invitations, Conference 1988 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Larry Siegel, Conference 1988 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Materials- miscellaneous, Conference 1988 (Box 7, Folder 25-27)
  - Miscellanous papers, Conference 1988 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - NALGAP, Conference 1988 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - NOID, Conference 1988 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Other mailing lists, Conference 1988 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Conference packet, Conference 1988 (Box 7, Folder 32-33)
  - Pamphlets (Boston area), Conference 1988 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Conference photos, Conference 1988 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Presentation session lists, Conference 1988 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Presenter photos and curricula vitae, Conference 1988 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Pride, Conference 1988 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Program book, Conference 1988 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Program book materials, Conference 1988 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Program books (completed), Conference 1988 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Proposals (alphabetical, by proposer?), Conference 1988 (Box 7, Folder 42-46)
  - Proposals (alphabetical, by proposer?), Conference 1988 (Box 8, Folder 1-17)
  - Remarks by Frank E. Young, Conference 1988 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Volunteer duties/hall duty, Conference 1988 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Volunteer duties/room monitors, Conference 1988 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Volunteer registration desk, Conference 1988 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - NLGHF-AAPHR "How May I Help You?" volunteer pins, Conference 1988 (Box 13)
  - VHS tape: AIDS Banquet- Speakers, Sat., July 23, 1988, V-369
  - Advertising, Conference 1989 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Advertising booklet, Conference 1989 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Agenda, Conference 1989 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Agenda addendum/changes, Conference 1989 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Alphabetical list of presentations, Conference 1989 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Caucuses: 12-step/basic, Conference 1989 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence re: RNs attending, Conference 1989 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Exhibits, Conference 1989 (Box 8, Folder 29-30)
  - Feedback, Conference 1989 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Institutes, Conference 1989 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous materials, Conference 1989 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Photo negatives, Conference 1989 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Poster session information, Conference 1989 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Poster session masters, Conference 1989 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Poster Session I, Conference 1989 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Poster Session II, Conference 1989 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Poster Session III, Conference 1989 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Poster Session IV, Conference 1989 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Poster Session V, Conference 1989 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Poster Session VI, Conference 1989 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Poster Session VII, Conference 1989 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Poster Session VIII, Conference 1989 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Poster Session IX, Conference 1989 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Poster Session X, Conference 1989 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Poster Session XI, Conference 1989 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Poster Session XII, Conference 1989 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - 11th National Lesbian and Gay Health Conference and 7th National AIDS Forum program books, Conference 1989 (Box 9, Folder 9-10)
  - Proposals, Conference 1989 (Box 9, Folder 11-13)
  - People With Aids (PWA), Conference 1989 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Room schedule, Conference 1989 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Sessions, Conference 1989 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Sessions: special interest, Conference 1989 (Box 9, Folder 17)